Field: A Is this vehicle being registered only for personal use, Type: /Btn
Field: I WANT TO, Type: /Btn
Field: Current Plate Number, Type: /Tx
Field: PRIMARY REGISTRANT Name Change, Type: /Btn
Field: PRIMARY REGISTRANT FORMER NAME, Type: /Tx
Field: CO-REGISTRANT Name Change, Type: /Btn
Field: CO-REGISTRANT EMAIL, Type: /Tx
Field: NYS New York State driver license ID Identification number of PRIMARY REGISTRANT, Type: /Tx
Field: PRIMARY REGISTRANT DATE OF BIRTH Month, Type: /Ch
Field: PRIMARY REGISTRANT DATE OF BIRTH Day, Type: /Ch
Field: PRIMARY REGISTRANT DATE OF BIRTH Year, Type: /Tx
Field: PRIMARY REGISTRANT SEX, Type: /Btn
Field: PRIMARY REGISTRANT TELEPHONE or MOBILE PHONE NUMBER Area Code, Type: /Tx
Field: PRIMARY REGISTRANT TELEPHONE or MOBILE PHONE NUMBER, Type: /Tx
Field: NYS New York State driver license ID Identification number of CO-REGISTRANT, Type: /Tx
Field: ADDRESS CHANGE, Type: /Btn
Field: CO-REGISTRANT DATE OF BIRTH Year, Type: /Tx
Field: CO-REGISTRANT DATE OF BIRTH Day, Type: /Ch
Field: CO-REGISTRANT DATE OF BIRTH Month, Type: /Ch
Field: CO-REGISTRANT SEX, Type: /Btn
Field: THE ADDRESS WHERE PRIMARY REGISTRANT GETS MAIL, Type: /Tx
Field: THE ADDRESS WHERE PRIMARY REGISTRANT GETS MAIL Apt Apartment No Number, Type: /Tx
Field: THE ADDRESS WHERE PRIMARY REGISTRANT GETS MAIL City or Town, Type: /Tx
Field: THE ADDRESS WHERE PRIMARY REGISTRANT GETS MAIL State, Type: /Ch
Field: THE ADDRESS WHERE PRIMARY REGISTRANT GETS MAIL Zip Code, Type: /Tx
Field: THE ADDRESS WHERE PRIMARY REGISTRANT RESIDES IF DIFFERENT FROM THE MAILING ADDRESS, Type: /Tx
Field: THE ADDRESS WHERE PRIMARY REGISTRANT RESIDES IF DIFFERENT FROM THE MAILING ADDRESS Apt Apartment No Number, Type: /Tx
Field: THE ADDRESS WHERE PRIMARY REGISTRANT RESIDES IF DIFFERENT FROM THE MAILING ADDRESS City or Town, Type: /Tx
Field: THE ADDRESS WHERE PRIMARY REGISTRANT RESIDES IF DIFFERENT FROM THE MAILING ADDRESS State, Type: /Ch
Field: THE ADDRESS WHERE PRIMARY REGISTRANT RESIDES IF DIFFERENT FROM THE MAILING ADDRESS Zip Code, Type: /Tx
Field: County of Residence, Type: /Tx
Field: Body Type, Type: /Btn
Field: VEHICLE DESCRIPTION Make, Type: /Tx
Field: VEHICLE DESCRIPTION Year, Type: /Tx
Field: VEHICLE IDENTIFICATION NUMBER, Type: /Tx
Field: Unladen Weight, Type: /Tx
Field: Color, Type: /Tx
Field: Type of Power Fuel, Type: /Btn
Field: Cylinders, Type: /Tx
Field: For trailers and commercial vehicles Maximum Gross Weight, Type: /Tx
Field: Adult Seating Capacity Including Driver, Type: /Tx
Field: Odometer Reading in Miles, Type: /Tx
Field: For commercial vehicles Axles, Type: /Tx
Field: For commercial vehicles Distance, Type: /Tx
Field: Is this vehicle a limousine stretch limousine or otherwise altered to increase seating capacity, Type: /Btn
Field: If YES is this limousine stretch limousine or otherwise altered vehicle equipped with safety belts at all occupant seating positions, Type: /Btn
Field: PRIMARY OWNER NYS New York State License Number, Type: /Tx
Field: PRIMARY OWNER DATE OF BIRTH Month, Type: /Ch
Field: PRIMARY OWNER DATE OF BIRTH Day, Type: /Ch
Field: PRIMARY OWNER DATE OF BIRTH Year, Type: /Tx
Field: PRIMARY OWNER SEX, Type: /Btn
Field: THE ADDRESS WHERE PRIMARY OWNER GETS MAIL, Type: /Tx
Field: THE ADDRESS WHERE PRIMARY OWNER GETS MAIL Apt Apartment No Number, Type: /Tx
Field: THE ADDRESS WHERE PRIMARY OWNER GETS MAIL City or Town, Type: /Tx
Field: THE ADDRESS WHERE PRIMARY OWNER GETS MAIL State, Type: /Ch
Field: THE ADDRESS WHERE PRIMARY OWNER GETS MAIL Zip Code, Type: /Tx
Field: THE ADDRESS WHERE PRIMARY OWNER GETS MAIL County, Type: /Tx
Field: NAME OF CO-OWNER, Type: /Tx
Field: Signature Date, Type: /Tx
Field: Has this vehicle been modified from the original manufacturer specifications without extending the chassis or lengthening the wheel base, Type: /Btn
Field: NONPERSONAL VEHICLE USE, Type: /Btn
Field: Other describe the use, Type: /Tx
Field: INSURANCE REQUIREMENTS For Hire direct or indirect compensation, Type: /Btn
Field: INSURANCE REQUIREMENTS Not For Hire, Type: /Btn
Field: INSURANCE REQUIREMENTS DOT Department of Transportation Operation, Type: /Btn
Field: NYS New York State DOT Department of Transportation Permit andor the Federal DOT Department of Transportation Permit number, Type: /Tx
Field: TAXIS ONLY, Type: /Btn
Field: Print Name Here, Type: /Tx
Field: Print Additional Name Here, Type: /Tx
Field: reset clear, Type: /Btn
Field: If this vehicle is a pickup truck that is never used for commercial purposes and does not have advertising on any part of the truck you are eligible for passenger plates or commercial plates, Type: /Btn
Field: NAME OF CO-REGISTRANT Last First Middle, Type: /Tx
Field: Type of Power Fuel Other please specify, Type: /Tx
Field: Body Type Other please specify, Type: /Tx
Field: NAME OF PRIMARY OWNER Last First Middle, Type: /Tx
Field: My signature authorizes the persons named in Section 1 to register this vehicle in that persons name I have provided the current ownership document, Type: /Btn
Field: NAME OF PRIMARY REGISTRANT Last First Middle or Business Name, Type: /Tx
Field: Has the vehicle been wrecked destroyed or damaged to such an extent that the total estimate or actual cost of parts and labor to rebuild or reconstruct the vehicle to the condition it was in before an accident and to make the vehicle legal to operate on the road or highways is more than 75 of the retail value of the vehicle at the time of loss, Type: /Btn
Field: Has this vehicle been modified from the original manufacturer specifications without extending the chassis or lengthening the wheel base If Yes describe the modifications, Type: /Tx
